Guide to the Stanford University Faculty Publications
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Pamphlets and Reprints, Series 2
  - Morgan, Bayard Q. (cont.) (Box 60)
  - Morgan, Theodore (Box 60)
  - Morrison, Stanley (Box 60)
  - Morse, William R. (Box 60)
  - Moser, Charles (Box 60)
  - Moser, Thomas (Box 60)
  - Moses, Paul J. (Box 60)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel (Box 60)
  - Mosher, Harry S. (Box 60)
  - Motherhead, John L. (Box 60)
  - Motley, James M. (Box 61)
  - Mozley, R. (Box 61)
  - Muller, Siemon W. (Box 61)
  - Mumford, Edward P. (Box 61)
  - Mumford, Lewis (Box 61)
  - Munro, W. B. (Box 61)
  - Murphy, D. W. (Box 61)
  - Murray, A. T. (Box 61)
  - Murray, Noreen E. (Box 61)
  - Muse, M. (Box 61)
  - Myers, George S. (Box 61)
  - Mysels, K. J. (Box 61)
  - Nachbar, William (Box 61)
  - Nagel, Gunther W. (Box 61)
  - Napier, B. Davie (Box 61)
  - Nash, Herbert C. (Box 61)
  - Needham, P. R. (Box 61)
  - Neidig, William (Box 61)
  - Neuhof, Mark (Box 62)
  - Neumark, S. D. (Box 62)
  - Newby, Hayes A. (Box 62)
  - Newcomb, R. W. (Box 62)
  - Newcomer, A. G. (Box 62)
  - Newel, Robert R. (Box 62)
  - Newsom, J. F. (Box 62)
  - Newton, Richard H. (Box 62)
  - Niebauer, John J. (Box 62)
  - Nielson, N. P. (Box 61)
  - Nielson, Oswald (Box 62)
  - Niu, Man Chiang (Box 62)
  - Nivison, David S. (Box 62)
  - North, Jeanne (Box 62)
  - North, Robert C. (Box 62)
  - O’Callaghan, Jerry A. (Box 62)
  - O’Connor, Gerald Brown (Box 62)
  - O’Malley, Charles D. (Box 62)
  - Oden, Melita H. (Box 62)
  - Oldroyd, Ida S. (Box 62)
  - Oliver, Jean Redmond (Box 62)
  - Olmstead, Frederick Law (Box 62)
  - Osborn, John C. (Box 62)
  - Osserman, Robert (Box 62)
  - Otis, Arthur S. (Box 63)
  - Oxley, G. M. (Box 63)
  - Packard, Earl L. (Box 63)
  - Packer, Herbert L. (Box 63)
  - Pagani, John (Box 63)
  - Page, Ben M. (Box 63)
  - Palmateer, T. J. (Box 63)
  - Panofsky, Wolfgang (Box 63)
  - Park, Charles F. (Box 63)
  - Park, Charles V. (Box 63)
  - Parker, Edwin W. (Box 63)
  - Parks, George A. (Box 63)
  - Parks, George S. (Box 63)
  - Parsons, Edward L. (Box 63)
  - Parsons, Harry G. (Box 63)
  - Parzen, Emanuel (Box 63)
  - Parzen, George (Box 63)
  - Patee, Howard H. (Box 63)
  - Pauling, Linus (Box 63)
  - Paulsen, James A. (Box 63)
  - Payne, Max B. (Box 63)
  - Payne, Rose (Box 63)
  - Pearson, Harold E. (Box 63)
  - Pearson, Lionel (Box 63)
  - Peffer, E. Louise (Box 63)
  - Peirce, George J. (Box 64)
  - Peiss, Clarence Norman (Box 64)
  - Pencharz, Richard (Box 64)
  - Perkins, David D. (Box 64)
  - Perkins, Herbert A. (Box 64)
  - Persike, Edward C. (Box 64)
  - Peterson, N. A. (Box 64)
  - Petit, Donald W. (Box 64)
  - Petit, Joseph M. (Box 64)
  - Philips, Dayton (Box 64)
  - Philips, R. S. (Box 64)
  - Piel, Carolyn S. (Box 64)
  - Pierson, Philip H. (Box 64)
  - Pike, Thomas (Box 64)
  - Pilgeram, Lawrence (Box 64)
  - Pillsbury, P. L. (Box 64)
  - Pischel, Dohrmann K. (Box 64)
  - Piston, Donald S. (Box 64)
  - Plotkin, Jack (Box 64)
  - Pollack, Robert S. (Box 64)
  - Polya, G. (Box 64)
  - Pool, Judith G. (Box 65)
  - Pooler, Jack (Box 65)
  - Popper, Jan (Box 65)
  - Posin, Jack (Box 65)
  - Possony, Stephan T. (Box 65)
  - Post, R. F. (Box 65)
  - Potter, David M. (Box 65)
  - Poulter, Thomas C. (Box 65)
  - Presseisen, Ernst L. (Box 65)
  - Presti, Joseph C. (Box 65)
  - Prewitt, Kenneth (Box 65)
  - Pribham, K. H. (Box 65)
  - Price, George C. (Box 65)
  - Price, John Basye (Box 65)
  - Proctor, W. G. (Box 65)
  - Prusmack, John J. (Box 65)
  - Pryor, Helen B. (Box 65)
  - Quillen, I. James (Box 66)
  - Rael, Juan B. (Box 66)
  - Raffel, Sidney (Box 66)
  - Rakestraw, Norris W. (Box 66)
  - Ralston, Jackson (Box 66)
  - Ramspeiger, Barbara (Box 66)
  - Rather, Lelland J. (Box 66)
  - Rau, Lucy (see also Lucy Rau Ferguson) (Box 66)
  - Rauch, Helene C. (Box 66)
  - Ravenhall, D. G. (Box 66)
  - Rawlins, A. G. (Box 66)
  - Ray, James C. (Box 66)
  - Read, J. Marion (Box 66)
  - Ready, W. B. (Box 66)
  - Reavis, James Clark (Box 66)
  - Reckendorf, Wolfgang M. (Box 66)
  - Reddi, V. G. K. (Box 66)
  - Reder, Melvin W. (Box 67)
  - Redlich, Dorothy (Box 67)
  - Reed, Alfred C. (Box 67)
  - Regnery, Dorothy (Box 67)
  - Reid, John T. (Box 67)
  - Reid, Whitelaw (Box 67)
  - Reighard, Edward (Box 67)
  - Reinhardt, Kurt F. (Box 67)
  - Rendtorff, Karl G. (Box 67)
  - Reynolds, D. K. (Box 67)
  - Reynolds, Leon B. (Box 67)
  - Rice, Carl C. (Box 67)
  - Rich, Willis H. (Box 67)
  - Richards, J. (Box 67)
  - Richardson, A. P. (Box 67)
  - Richardson, George M. (Box 67)
  - Richardson, R. E. (Box 67)
  - Richtmyer, Robert (Box 68)
  - Rieber, Charles H. (Box 68)
  - Rieber, F. (Box 68)
  - Ringruse, Edward (Box 68)
  - Roantree, Robert J. (Box 68)
  - Robbins, Edward (Box 68)
  - Robbins, Irving (Box 68)
  - Roberts, Holland D. (Box 68)
  - Roberts, Seymour R. (Box 68)
  - Robertson, O. H. (Box 68)
  - Robichek, Alexander A. (Box 68)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene (Box 68)
  - Robinson, Saul J. (Box 68)
  - Robson, Bernard (Box 68)
  - Roderick, H. (Box 68)
  - Rodin, F. H. (Box 68)
  - Roehrig, F. L. O. (Box 69)
  - Roelofs, Howard (Box 69)
  - Rogers, Austin F. (Box 69)
  - Rogers, E. H. (Box 70)
  - Rogers, F. J. (Box 70)
  - Roggereen, Vincent J. (Box 70)
  - Rolfe, H. W. (Box 70)
  - Rollins, Reed C. (Box 70)
  - Rosenhan, D. L. (Box 70)
  - Rosenzweig, Robert (Box 70)
  - Ross, P. A. (Box 70)
  - Ross, Raymond R. (Box 70)
  - Ross, Sydney (Box 70)
  - Roth, Almon E. (Box 70)
  - Roth, Bernard (Box 70)
  - Rourke, Anthony (Box 70)
  - Rowe, George H. (Box 70)
  - Royden, H. L. (Box 70)
  - Rubin, H. (Box 70)
  - Rubin, Norma (Box 70)
  - Rubinstein, L. J. (Box 70)
  - Ruch, Marian S. (Box 70)
  - Ruff, Wesley K. (Box 70)
  - Rugtiv, George M. (Box 70)
  - Ruppenthal, Karl M. (Box 70)
  - Russell, D. L. (Box 70)
  - Russell, Frances Theresa (Box 70)
  - Russell, Frank M. (Box 70)
  - Rutherford, Miriam (Box 70)
  - Ryan, Harris Joseph (Box 70)
  - Ryan, Lawrence (Box 70)
  - Rytand, David A. (Box 70)
  - Sabine, George H. (Box 70)
  - Sadusk, Joseph F. (Box 70)
  - Sahyun, Melville (Box 71)
  - Samilson, Robert L. (Box 71)
  - Samson, Paul C. (Box 71)
  - Sandberg, Eugene C. (Box 71)
  - Sanders, Harry (missing, paged 1992) (Box 71)
  - Sanford, Fernando (Box 71)
  - Sanford, Nevitt (Box 71)
  - Sangiorgi, R. B. (Box 71)
  - Saunders, William W. (Box 71)
  - Savelle, Max (Box 71)
  - Sawyer, Frederick G. (Box 72)
  - Schaeffer, A. C. (Box 72)
  - Schaller, Walter F. (Box 72)
  - Schaupp, John B. (Box 72)
  - Schawlow, Arthur L. (Box 72)
  - Schell, Robert F. (Box 72)
  - Schellinger, A. Kenneth (Box 72)
  - Schenck, Hubert G. (Box 5)
  - Schenck, Hubert G. (Box 6)
  - Schenk, Hubert G. (Box 72)
  - Schepler, Herman C. (Box 72)
  - Schevill, Isabel M. (Box 72)
  - Schiff, Leonard I. (Box 72)
  - Schilling, Walter (Box 72)
  - Schmidt, Harold C. (Box 72)
  - Schmidt, Otto E. L. (Box 72)
  - Schofield, Mary (Box 73)
  - Schramm, Wilbur B. (Box 72)
  - Schrier, Stanley L. (Box 72)
  - Schuekle, Gertrude (Box 72)
  - Schulte, T. L. (Box 72)
  - Schultz, Edwin (Box 72)
  - Schultz, Edwin (cont.) (Box 73)
  - Schurman, Jacob (Box 73)
  - Schwartz, William H. (Box 73)
  - Schwartz, William L. (Box 73)
  - Schwarz, Gideon (Box 73)
  - Schwerdt, Carlton E. (Box 73)
  - Scott, Richard (Box 73)
  - Scull, Alvis Joe (Box 73)
  - Sears, H. J. (Box 73)
  - Sears, Jesse B. (Box 73)
  - Sears, Pauline S. (Box 73)
  - Sears, Robert R. (Box 74)
  - Seid, Martin J. (Box 74)
  - Seifert, H. S. (Box 74)
  - Sellards, John A. (Box 74)
  - Selzer, Arthur (Box 74)
  - Semans, Sarah (Box 74)
  - Semelyen, J. A. (Box 74)
  - Senz, Edward H. (Box 74)
  - Sethuraman, J. (Box 74)
  - Sewall, Cecil (Box 74)
  - Seward, S. S., Jr. (Box 74)
  - Shafer, George Daniel (Box 74)
  - Shallenberger, Frank K. (Box 74)
  - Shapiro, Martin (Box 74)
  - Shapiro, Mel (Box 74)
  - Sharp, Gordon (Box 74)
  - Sharp, William L. (Box 74)
  - Sharpe, Otis Allen (Box 74)
  - Sharpe, William F. (Box 74)
  - Shedd, Solon (Box 74)
  - Shepard, Charles E. (Box 74)
  - Shepard, O. Cutler (Box 74)
  - Shepard, William P. (Box 74)
  - Sher, Byron D. (Box 74)
  - Sherby, Olga D. (Box 74)
  - Sheshinsky, Eytan (Box 74)
  - Shidler, Frederick P. (Box 74)
  - Shirley, Hale F. (Box 74)
  - Shockley, William B. (Box 74)
  - Shockley, William H. (Box 74)
  - Shooter, E. M. (Box 74)
  - Shoven, John B. (Box 74)
  - Show, Arley B. (Box 74)
  - Shumate, Charles A. (Box 75)
  - Shumway, Norman E. (Box 75)
  - Siegel, Benjamin V. (Box 75)
  - Siegel, Sidney (Box 75)
  - Sigurdson, Larus A. (Box 75)
  - Silberling, Norman J. (Box 75)
  - Simmons, F. Blair (Box 75)
  - Simon, Walter M. (Box 75)
  - Simpson, Claude M. (Box 75)
  - Simpson, Paul G. (Box 75)
  - Singh, Vikramaditya (Box 75)
  - Skilling, Hugh (Box 75)
  - Skinner, M. M. (Box 75)
  - Skocpol, Theda (Box 75)
  - Skogsberg, Tage (Box 75)
  - Skoog, Douglas A. (Box 75)
  - Slonaker, James R. (Box 75)
  - Slonaker, James R., [on the White Rat] (Box 89)
  - Slusser, Robert M. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Albert W. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Dan T. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Daniel M. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Everett W. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Gilbert Morgan (Box 76)
  - Smith, James K. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Joseph (Box 76)
  - Smith, Philip E. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Ray C. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Robert L. (Box 76)
  - Smith, Stanley Astredo (Box 76)
  - Smith, Wendy (Box 76)
  - Snodgrass, Robert E. (Box 76)
  - Snow, William F. (Box 76)
  - Soare, Orland A. (Box 76)
  - Sokol, Anthony E. (Box 76)
  - Solomon, George F. (Box 77)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander (Box 77)
  - Spaet, Theodore H. (Box 77)
  - Spaeth, Carl B. (Box 77)
  - Spalding, Alfred B. (Box 77)
  - Spangenberg, Karl R. (Box 77)
  - Speigelberg, Frederic (Box 77)
  - Spence, Andrew M. (Box 77)
  - Spencer, Donald C. (Box 77)
  - Spindler, George D. (Box 77)
  - Spitz, Lewis W. (Box 77)
  - Spoehr, Hermann A. (Box 77)
  - Starbuck, Edwin P. (Box 77)
  - Starks, Edwin C. (Box 77)
  - Stearns, Herman D. (Box 78)
  - Stebbins, Horatio (Box 78)
  - Steere, William C. (Box 78)
  - Stegner, Wallace (Box 78)
  - Stephenson, Henry A. (Box 78)
  - Sterling, J. E. W. (Box 78)
  - Stetefeldt, C. A. (Box 78)
  - Steward, John P. (Box 78)
  - Stewart, Kenneth (Box 78)
  - Stiglitz, Joseph E. (Box 78)
  - Stillman, John Maxson (Box 78)
  - Stolz, Lois Meek (Box 78)
  - Stone, James H. (Box 78)
  - Storey, Margaret (Box 78)
  - Storey, Thomas A. (Box 6)
  - Storey, Thomas A. (Box 7)
  - Storey, Thomas A. (Box 78)
  - Stowe, Lyman M. (Box 78)
  - Street, Robert L. (Box 78)
  - Strong, Edward K. (Box 78)
  - Strothman, Friedrich (Box 79)
  - Stuart, Graham H. (Box 79)
  - Stuart, Henry W. (Box 79)
  - Sturrock, Peter A. (Box 79)
  - Sullivan, Julia C. (Box 79)
  - Suppes, Patrick (Box 79)
  - Sutherland, Alex J. (Box 80)
  - Swain, Robert E. (Box 80)
  - Swank, Raynard C. (Box 80)
  - Sworakowski, Witold (Box 80)
  - Tai, C. T. (Box 80)
  - Tainter, Maurice L. (Box 80)
  - Taketa, S. Tom (Box 80)
  - Tamler, Edward (Box 80)
  - Tart, Charles T. (Box 80)
  - Tartlock, John S. P. (Box 80)
  - Tatum, E. L. (Box 80)
  - Taylor, Alonzo E. (Box 80)
  - Taylor, Charles V. (Box 81)
  - Taylor, Donald W. (Box 81)
  - Taylor, Frank J. (Box 81)
  - Teggart, Frederick J. (Box 81)
  - Terman, Frederick E. (Box 81)
  - Terman, Lewis M. (Box 81)
  - Terry, Marcus C. (Box 81)
  - Thalmann, Hans E. (Box 81)
  - Thelander, H. E. (Box 81)
  - Thoburn, Wilbur Wilson (Box 81)
  - Thomas, John H. (Box 81)
  - Thomas, John O. (Box 81)
  - Thomas, Lawrence G. (Box 81)
  - Thomas, Sidney F. (Box 81)
  - Thompson, Mary C. (Box 81)
  - Thompson, William F. (Box 81)
  - Thornhill, C. E. (Box 81)
  - Thurman, Samuel D., Jr. (Box 82)
  - Tickell, Frederick (Box 82)
  - Timoshenko, Stephen P. (Box 82)
  - Timoshenko, Vladimir P. (Box 82)
  - Tinker, Miles A. (Box 82)
  - Todd, Lois Pendleton (Box 82)
  - Tolman, Cyrus F. (Box 82)
  - Tomkins, Pendleton (Box 82)
  - Torrey, Harry Beal (Box 82)
  - Townley, Sidney Dean (Box 82)
  - Travis, Martin B. (Box 82)
  - Travis, Roland C. (Box 82)
  - Treat, Payson J. (Box 83)
  - Tressider, Donald (Box 82)
  - Trimble, Harold G. (Box 82)
  - Tripi, Helen B. (Box 82)
  - Triska, Jan F. (Box 82)
  - Trotter, Reginald George (Box 83)
  - Troxell, John P. (Box 83)
  - Trueblood, Elton (Box 83)
  - Tsuboi, Kenneth K. (Box 83)
  - Tucker, Dan (Box 83)
  - Tum, Suden Linda (Box 83)
  - Turkel, Henry W. (Box 83)
  - Turner, Margaret L. (Box 83)
  - Turner, Robert Stuart (Box 83)
  - Turrentine, Lowell (Box 83)
  - Twitty, Victor Chandler (Box 83)
  - Uspensky, James Victor (Box 83)
  - Uzawa, Hirofumi (Box 83)
  - Van Dyke, Milton (Box 83)
  - Van Neil, C. B. (Box 83)
  - Van Patten, Nathan (Box 84)
  - Van Rysselberghe, Pierre (Box 84)
  - Van Slyke, Lyman P. (Box 84)
  - Van Winkle, W., Jr. (Box 84)
  - Vanderhoof, V. L. (Box 83)
  - Varian, Russell H. (Box 84)
  - Veblen, Thorstein B. (Box 84)
  - Verba, Sidney (Box 84)
  - Vernier, Chester G. (Box 84)
  - Vestal, A. G. (Box 85)
  - Villard, Oswald G. (Box 85)
  - Vincenti, Walter G. (Box 85)
  - Vold, Robert D. (Box 85)
  - Volkurt, Edmund H. (Box 85)
  - Von der Groeben, J. (Box 38)
  - Vosti, Kenneth L. (Box 85)
  - Voyce, Arthur (Box 85)
  - Vucinich, Wayne S. (Box 85)
  - Wade, G. (Box 85)
  - Walker, Douglas R. (Box 85)
  - Ward, William C. (Box 85)
  - Waring, Gerald A. (Box 85)
  - Warmbrunn, Werner (Box 85)
  - Warner, Glenn S. (Box 85)
  - Warren, J. M. (Box 85)
  - Wasserman, Karlman (Box 85)
  - Waterman, Alan T. (Box 85)
  - Waters, Aaron C. (Box 85)
  - Watkins, D. A. (Box 85)
  - Watkins, James T. (Box 85)
  - Watt, Ian (Box 85)
  - Waxler, Samuel H. (Box 85)
  - Way, Stuart C. (Box 85)
  - Wayburn, Edgar (Box 85)
  - Weaver, Ellen C. (Box 85)
  - Weber, David L. (Box 85)
  - Webster, David Locke (Box 85)
  - Webster, Hutton (Box 86)
  - Weed, Luell (Box 86)
  - Weigle, Clifford F. (Box 86)
  - Weinstein, Boris (Box 86)
  - Weinstock, Robert (Box 86)
  - Weisskopf, Alex (Box 86)
  - Weissman, S. R. (Box 86)
  - Wert, Robert J. (Box 86)
  - West, Victor J. (Box 86)
  - Westburg, V. B. (Box 86)
  - Westdahl, Philip R. (Box 86)
  - Wexler, Bernard C. (Box 86)
  - Weymouth, Frank W. (Box 86)
  - Weyrauch, Henry M. (Box 86)
  - Whitaker, Albert Conser (Box 86)
  - Whitaker, Douglas M. (Box 86)
  - Whitaker, Virgil K. (Box 86)
  - White, Andrew Dickson (Box 86)
  - White, C. Langdon (Box 86)
  - White, Lynn, Jr. (Box 86)
  - Whitney, Elizabeth G. (Box 86)
  - Wickersheim, K. A. (Box 86)
  - Wickizer, Vernon D. (Box 86)
  - Widrow, Bernard (Box 86)
  - Wiggins, Ira L. (Box 86)
  - Wilbur, Dwight L. (Box 87)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman (Box 87)
  - Wildman, Murray Shipley (Box 87)
  - Willard, Oliver M. (Box 87)
  - Willett, Forrest M. (Box 87)
  - Williams, Harry A. (Box 87)
  - Williams, Joseph E. (Box 87)
  - Willis, Bailey (Box 8)
  - Willis, Bailey (Box 9)
  - Willis, Bailey (Box 87)
  - Wilmer, Harry A. (Box 87)
  - Wilson, George T. (Box 87)
  - Wilson, Perry (Box 87)
  - Wilson, Robert B. (Box 87)
  - Winbigler, H. Donald (Box 87)
  - Winder, Clarence L. (Box 87)
  - Windholz, Frank (Box 87)
  - Wing, Charles B. (Box 87)
  - Winslow, D. K. (Box 87)
  - Winters, Yvors (Box 87)
  - Wise, Lauress L. (Box 88)
  - Wohlschlag, Donald E. (Box 88)
  - Wolfe, Bertram D. (Box 88)
  - Wood, Casey A. (Box 88)
  - Wood, David A. (Box 88)
  - Wood, Peter D. (Box 88)
  - Wood, Thomas D. (Box 88)
  - Woodward, Frederick C. (Box 88)
  - Work, James A. (Box 88)
  - Working, Holbrook (Box 88)
  - Worthington, Catherine (Box 88)
  - Wrenn, C. Gilbert (Box 88)